He still hasn't responded.
What's taking him so long?
Do you really want him to write back?
I do. No matter how he responds,
I'm going to destroy him with a picture of a bored cat saying,
Oh, really?
Meanwhile.
What are you doing?
I've created some other user accounts so I can post positive comments about their paper.
This wee lil' bairn of a theory nearly blew my kilt off?
You have to read it how Dr. Angus McDougall of the University of Edinburgh would.
This wee lil' bairn of theory nearly blew me kilt off.
He wrote back.
Cooper and Hofstadter resorting to juvenile attempts at humor is proof they have nothing to back up their ridiculous paper.
It should come as no surprise given they work at Cal Tech, essentially a technical school where even the physicists are basically engineers.
Engineers.
Do you know how insulting that is?
Yes.
Guys, this person's just going out of their way to get a rise out of you.
Yeah, but it's still so aggravating.
All the other comments said really nice things. Focus on those.
Yeah.
Dr. Dimitri Plankovic of Moscow University said,
This paper great. I love it more than vodka.
See? Better with the accent.
And send.
What did you write?
I'm done hiding from bullies. I am taking this into the real world.
What does that mean?
I told him we'll meet him face to face anytime, anywhere.
Are you crazy? You don't know who this person is? Delete that!
Come on, Sheldon.
Okay, okay. Calm down.
It's him. He's trying to video chat.
Perhaps I shouldn't have taken this into the real world.
Oh, really?
I'm so sick of people being mean on the internet.
I think the anonymity makes everyone feel like they can say things they'd never say to your face.
Interesting.
I can't think of a single thing I wouldn't say to someone's face.
Never noticed that about you.
You know what? At least you guys did something.
You know, you had a theory. You wrote a paper. You made an actual contribution.
All guys like this do is just tear down other people's work.
He's right.
Yeah, I say we call this person back.
We've got no reason to hide.
All right, do it. Call him. Let's find out what this loser's ever accomplished.
Click it with me.
One, two, three, click.
Well, hello there.
Professor Hawking?
Oh, brother, you should see the look on your faces.
You really didn't like our paper?
I like your paper very much. The premise is intriguing.
Then why are you attacking us?
If you were sitting in a chair for 40 years, you'd get bored too.
Anyway, gotta go. I promise to help the neighbor kid with his math homework.
Ciao.
Stephen Hawking liked our paper.
Said the premise is intriguing.
Good to see you again, Mr. Stephen Hawking liked our paper.
And you as well, Mr., our premise is intriguing.
Still huh?
I'll admit that's pretty cool.
Yeah, you keep setting me up for failure.
Hey, is this person just going out of their way
to get a rise out of you?
Yeah, that oughta get a rise out of her.
Yeah, but it's still so aggravating.
Yeah, but it's still a risk for everything else
Who are you?
It's aggravating, isn't it, when someone won't answer your questions.
your questions.
Said the premise is intriguing.
Sounds intriguing?
Not you, you need to be stitched up.
Yeah, you keep setting me up for failure.
Yeah, but it's still so aggravating.
Said the premise is intriguing.
Yeah, you keep setting me up for failure.
Hey, is this person just going out of their way
to get a rise out of you?
Yeah, but it's still so aggravating.
Said the premise is intriguing.
Yeah, you keep setting me up for failure.